open lid
put lid
turn off hot
grab spoon
put lid
pick up sauce
start rice
spoon rice into the lunch box
pat down rice
spoon rice
Put saucepan
Take saucepan
Scoop food
Spoon food
Put down saucepan
Pick up lid
Put lid
turn on tap
put spoon
rinse saucepan
turn off tap
pour water
grab saucepan
put down lid
fill saucepan
rinse saucepan
turn off tap
pour water
grab sponge
wash lid
put lid in drying rack
grab sauce pan
wash sauce pan
continue washing sauce pan
put saucepan in drying rack
put on each box
pour water
grab spoon
wash spoon
put spoon
pour water
put bowl
turn on tap
rinse
sponge
clean side
clean sink
clean plug
put plug
wipe sink
grab plug
empty plug in bin
put lid on bin
put plug in sink
turn on tap
clean side
rinse bowl
clean bowl
move tap
turn off tap
clean side
put sponge
dry hands
put lid on lunch box
grab lid
grab lunch boxes
open fridge
put lunch box in fridge
close fridge
grab grape
*BLANK CLIP*
[END SUBTITLE]